♪♪♪
- Hi, Honey. How you doin'?
- I'm doin' good.
How are you doin'?
- What's your name?
- Billy.
- Ohh. I like that name.
Have you been a good little boy?
- Yes. (laughs) Yes.
- How old are you, Billy?
- I'm 26. I'm an entertainment
lawyer in Beverly Hills.
♪ Sweet emotion ♪
♪ You talk about things
that nobody cares ♪
- Guess what I'm wearing, Billy.
♪ Wearing out things
that nobody wears ♪
♪ You're calling my name
but I gotta make clear ♪
- Silk, see-through mini skirt.
♪ I can't say, baby,
where I'll be in a year ♪
- Nice panties underneath.
♪ Some sweat hog mama
with a face like a gent ♪
♪ Said my get up and go,
must've got up and went ♪
♪ Well I got good news,
she's a real good liar ♪
♪ 'Cause the backstage boogie
sets your pants on fire ♪
- I wouldn't lie, Billy.
♪ Sweet emotion ♪
♪ I pulled into town
in a police car ♪
♪ Your daddy said I took
it just a little too far ♪
- Well, Billy.
♪ You're telling her things
but your girlfriend lied ♪
- What are you gonna do to me?
♪ You can't catch me 'cause
the rabbit done died ♪
♪ Yes it did ♪
- Yes, Billy.
♪ Stand in the front
just a shakin' your ass ♪
- What else?
♪ I'll take you backstage,
you can drink from my glass ♪
♪ I'll talk about something
you can sure understand ♪
- Can you hold on
for just a second?
♪ 'Cause a month on the road and
I'll be eating from your hand ♪
- Is that all, Billy?
(guitar solo)
(music fading)
- It's been real fun, Billy.
(phone clicking)
- (laughs) Yeah.
- Call me again
some time, Honey.
(baby crying)
(phone clicking)